女主持人：奥巴马卸任总统 他和家人将继续
Female Speaker: The Obama's are staying in D.C. for two
住在华盛顿特区二年
years after the President leaves office.
Chuck Todd：奥巴马既将从三军统帅
Chuck Todd: He's about to go from Commander in Chief
变成沙发统帅
to Couch Commander.
总统： - 去你的，查克托德。
The President: -- you, Chuck Todd.
但我这二年在华盛顿特区要干嘛？
What am I going to do in D.C. for two years?
（音乐）
(music)
副总统：就去伦敦访问吧，
The Vice President: Get around to London,
总统先生。
Mr. President.
总统：我总不可能每天飞伦敦，对吧？
The President: I can't go every day, can I?
副总统：你比较喜欢哪一副？
The Vice President: Which do you like better?
这一副？
These?
还是这一副？
Or These?
总统：乔，这两副根本一模一样。
The President: Joe, they're the same.
副总统：这两副呈现不同的心情啊。
The Vice President: They capture different moods.
总统：乔，可以专心在正事上吗？
The President: Joe, I need some focus here.
副总统：你选在我保养墨镜时来烦我
The Vice President: Coming in here during aviator time,
还觉得自己的事最…
thinks everything --
总统：不好意思 你在碎念啥？
The President: I'm sorry, what's that?
副总统：我是说 总统先生
The Vice President: I said, Mr. President,
你要实际一点
you got to be practical.
你卸任后就可以开车了。
And look, you can drive again,
你需要驾照
you're going to need a license.
你是运动迷，你可以向华盛顿特区的球队毛遂自荐啊？
You love sports, why don't you volunteer to work one of
the teams around here?
（音乐）
(music)
总统：这是华盛顿奇才队吗？
The President: Is this the Washington Wizards?
我听说你们需要个教练
I understand you're looking for some coaching help.
我跟你讲 我以前指导过几次我闺女的球队
Let's just say I coached my daughter's team a few times.
喂？
Hello?
（音乐）
(music)
女演员：44。
Female Speaker: 44.
总统：终于轮到我了
The President: Finally.
我会在华盛顿待一段时间
So, I'm going to be in D.C. for awhile,
我觉得我得重新开始开车
and I thought I'd take up driving again.
女演员：你叫什么名字？
Female Speaker: What's the name?
总统：巴拉克·侯赛因·奥巴马。
The President: Barack Hussein Obama.
女演员：天啦
Female Speaker: Yikes.
好吧 鉴于你没有驾照
Well, since you don't have a driver's license,
你必须出示出生证明
you're going to need a birth certificate.
总统：是吗？
The President: Really?
女演员：没错
Female Speaker: Really.
总统：这是真的。
The President: It's real.
女演员：是吗？
Female Speaker: Is it?
总统：真的是真的。
The President: It's real.
女演员：是么？
Female Speaker: But is it?
（音乐）
(music)
总统：哦。
The President: Oh.
米歇尔忘带了她的手机。
Michelle left her phone.
来我们看看。
Let's see here.
哈。
Huh.
她居然还有Snapchat。
She's got Snapchat.
奥巴马超赞！
Obamacare is great!
而且真有用！
And it's really working!
现在就加入！
Sign up now!
男主讲人：最新新闻。
Male Speaker: Breaking news.
Wolf Blitzer：米歇尔 奥巴马
Wolf Blitzer: Michelle Obama in hot water,
因为发布此视频深陷风波
after posting this video earlier today.
总统：奥巴马超赞！
The President: Obamacare is great!
而且真有用！
And it's really working!
现在就加入！
Sign up now!
不好吗？
No?
奥巴马夫人：不。
Mrs. Obama: No.
总统：起码收率数更高啊
The President: Did it get a lot of views, at least?
奥巴马太太：亲爱的，够了。
Mrs. Obama: Honey, enough.
够了。
Enough.
为什么你不能去找找那些早已退休的老司机聊聊呢
Why don't you just talk to somebody who has been
through this.
我现在去骑动感单车了
I got to go to SoulCycle.
总统：她是对的。
The President: She's right.
我知道我该找谁了
I know who I need to talk to.
嗨。
Hey.
我是巴拉克。
It's Barack.
听着，我们一起聚聚下。
Listen, could we get together.
（音乐）
(music)
这真是一部好片。
Now that is a great movie.
约翰·博纳：是的。
John Boehner: Yeah.
每次看着很感动
It gets me every time.
汤姆·汉克斯：再见了，小伙伴。
Tom Hanks: So long, partner.
（音乐）
(music)
总统：所以，有什么建议给我不？
The President: So, you got any advice for me?
John Boehner：你现在想起来听我的建议了啊？
John Boehner: So now you want my advice?
首先，不要再给我领英邀请了好不好
First, stop sending me all these LinkedIn requests.
然后，这事儿的妙处在于
And second, here's the beauty of this whole thing.
你现在有大把时间想清楚了
You've got all the time in the world to figure this out.
你可以做一会儿你自己了
You can just be you for awhile.
如果你知道你是啥样
If you know how to do that again.
总统：所以我可以做我自己了
The President: So I can just be me.
（音乐）
(music)
我现在可以安心穿上我的妈妈裤了
And I can wear my mom jeans in peace.
我不喜欢这条牛仔裤
I hate these tight jeans.
约翰·博纳：很好
John Boehner: That's good.
很好
That's good.
昨天我中午11:30就喝了瓶啤酒。
Yesterday, I had a beer at 11:30 in the morning.
现在麦当劳全天都卖了早餐
And you know, McDonalds now serves breakfast all day long.
总统：米歇尔现在在上单车课
The President: And Michelle's going to be at
所以她不会发现的
spin class, so she'll never know.
约翰·博纳：对。
John Boehner: Right.
看开一点
Let it go.
时间不会久，你很快就能走出
And it won't be long, you'll be able to walk right out of
白宫总统办公室了 一边唱着蚂蚁呀嘿
the Oval Office singing Zip-a-Dee-Doo-Dah
蚂蚁呀嘿
Zip-a-Dee-Day.
（语言）
(laughter)
然后你还有大把时间去沐浴阳光 晒出美黑
And you've got plenty of time to work on your tan.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
我终于谈成了一笔大交易  买到了一台雪佛兰太浩车
I finally got the grand bargain on a sweet Chevy Tahoe.
看这个
Look here.
看
想要吗？
You want one?
Wolf Blitzer：最新新闻。
Wolf Blitzer: Breaking news.
前总统巴拉克·奥巴马今年打了第347轮
Former President Barack Obama on his 347th round of
高尔夫球，这是很棒的事情。
golf for the year, and it's totally great.
格洛丽亚，这回没有什么问题
And Gloria, not a problem for anybody.
格洛丽亚·博格：我想不到让我想在乎的理由，沃夫
Gloria Borger: I can't think of a reason to care, Wolf.
相信我，我想了很久。
And believe me, I've tried.
（音乐）
(music)